ILR School Library Course Outline and Reading Lists /4076
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Library Course Outline and Reading Lists
1947-1950
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4076
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3111357
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 27, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4006: Martin P. Catherwood Library Circulation Department Reserve Lists /4012: Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List /4044: Martin P. Catherwood Library Circulation Department Reserve Reading List Additional
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; Martin P. Catherwood Library
3111357
- Readings and Courses Materials Spring 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Readings and Course Materials Fall 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Readings and Course Materials Fall, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Readings and Course Materials Fall 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Readings and Course Materials Spring 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Readings and Materials Fall 1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Readings and Course Materials Spring 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Readings and Course Materials Spring and Fall 1947 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Readings and Course Materials Spring 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Course Materials, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)